Curriculum Vitae

Nikita Norov

About me

Hyperactive programmer. With teamwork and freelance experience.

Always ready to learn new things like new technologies and goodies.

I started my programmer life with JS and game modding and, after that,

I moved for a long time to Android on Java. Last half year learned Android Kotlin + Native Kotlin.

About my hobbies..., I love to play games, also enjoy fixing various electronics to kill time.

Isokatu 73, 90120 Oulu | +358401743060 | nikita.norov.2002@gmail.com

My webpage (Unavaible right now)

Github | Linkedin | Telegram | Google Play | stackoverflow

Public Portfolio

Name	Position	Stack	Status
GitHub	PCB designer, Main developer	Arduino, C++, PlatformIO, KiCAD	Order: Make a PCB board and code for Arduino based on the prototype of spot welding In the progress (Branch: master)

Name	Position	Stack	Status
Cars USSR	Main developer	Android, Java, Kotlin, Asset, Markdown, NavigationUI, Kotlin DSL, DataBining, Glide, AdMob, SharedPreference, Android Legacy	The oldest and partly the best project, because it was made with a soul and taught me a lot. It's coming to an end for now The last update will be released in 2022
			Google Play
KotlinGallery	Main developer	Android, Kotlin, Asset, Koin, Retrofit, Glide, NavigationUI, DataBining	First project for learn Koin + Retrofit and trying undestand Dependens Injection Ended: Jul 17, 2021 (Branch: master)
МаіnWindow — С X Тут латиница, а справа выхлоп Туt natuńuęa, a cbpaßa ßńlxnob Replace	Main developer	C++, Qt5, Kotlin, TornadoFX, Python	Friend asked to create a translator for game [Cyrillic -> Latin (transcript cyrillic)] Ended: Jul 3, 2021 (Branch: master)

Name	Position	Stack	Status
COFFEEBREAKER Technology & convenient	Project Manager, Main Java Android Developer, Moral support of the team	Android, Java, Java HTTP (API Requests), Android SDK, UI/UX, Picasso	The project was frozen due to design and architecture problems. At the moment I am rewriting a mobile application in Kotlin with a new design Ended: Jul 20, 2020 (Branch: AndroidRefactor)
GitHub	Android Java Developer, Team Leader	Android, Java, Constraint Layout Release	School project with random student Ended: Sep 17, 2019 (Branch: master)
Wallpaper App AND AND TOWNS	Main developer	Android, Java, Asset, RecyclerView, Glide	Some experements with assets and recyclerview on java Ended: Jun 8, 2019 (Branch: master)
	I have work that not yet added to this list.	Currently writing README for another repo's	

Education

Location	Year
----------	------

Location	Year
Electronics Technician, OSAO Kaukovainio unit	8.2018 ~ 9.2021
Primary school	2009 ~ 2018

Courses

Course	Year
Occupational Safety card, OSAO Kaukovainio unit	2018 ~ 2024
Electrical Safety card, OSAO Kaukovainio unit	2018 ~ 2024
First aid course, OSAO Kaukovainio unit	2018 ~ 2022
Fire work card, OSAO Kaukovainio unit	2018 ~ 2023
Hygiene passport, OSAO	2019 ~ Endless

Work experience

Place	Position	Year
Freelance	Android Software Developer	2019 ~ Now
Riots	Electronics Technician	1.2021 ~ 3.2021
SPR-Kontti	Device tester and vendor	7.2020 ~ 8.2020
iLOQ	Production	11.2019 ~ 1.2020
Jäätelökioski, 4H	Seller	7.2019 ~ 8.2019
Jäätelökioski, 4H	Seller	6.2018 ~ 7.2018
K-market	Seller	3.2018 ~ 4.2018
Posti	Sorter	4.2017 ~ 5.2017

Skills

IT

Programming

Programming languages Stack	
-----------------------------	--

Programming languages	Stack
Java	Android, JavaFX, Forge
Kotlin	Android, Koin, Retrofit, TornadoFX, JetPack NavigationUI
C++	Qt5 Desktop, Arduino

Software

Арр	Туре	Level
Libre office	Office	Basic
KiCAD	CAD	Basic
Git	Vesion Contril	Good
Linux	Operation System	Main
MacOS	Operation System	Basic
Windows	Operation System	Hate
JetBrains Software	IDE	Good
VS Code	IDE	Good

Language

Language	Level
Russian	Native
Finnish	Great
English	Intermediate
Ukrainian	Understand